<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>ckunte.net log</title><link>"http://blog.example.com/"rss.xml</link><description>ckunte.net log</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 23:15:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.0.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Third Post</title><link>"http://blog.example.com/"2013/third-post</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This is my third post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my third post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The End&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Chyetanya Kunte</author><guid isPermaLink="true">"http://blog.example.com/"2013/third-post</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Second Post</title><link>"http://blog.example.com/"2012/second-post</link><description>&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since I posted the first post, but that is okey. I am ok, you are ok. We are all ok.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The End&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Chyetanya Kunte</author><guid isPermaLink="true">"http://blog.example.com/"2012/second-post</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>"http://blog.example.com/"1970/first-post</link><description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it. This is my first post and I am sticking to it. It is a simple post, but that is the way I like it.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The End&lt;/p&gt;</description><author>Chyetanya Kunte</author><guid isPermaLink="true">"http://blog.example.com/"1970/first-post</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>